■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
安排妥当了吗
Have you made the preparations?
确定现在就要走吗  上校
Are you sure you want to leave now, colonel?
朱玛将军要是知道你放弃任务
Can't imagine general juma will be pleased
肯定不会高兴的
To learn that you're abandoning your mission.
任务已经没戏了
The mission is over.
你以为我傻吗  伯内特先生
You think i'm a fool, mr. burnett?
如果在我出境的路上
If anything should happen to me
遭遇任何不测
on my way out of the country
这份牵扯到所有人的名单
The data file with all the names and bank transactions
还有银行交易明细的文件
Of all those involved will be
就会被送去司法部门
sent to the justice department
车到了以后
When the car arrives, we would like you
我们希望你能上车跟司机走
To go with the driver
以便我们能跟着你顺藤摸瓜找到杜巴库
So that we could follow you back to dubaku.
你要她去找杜巴库吗
You want her to go to him and face him?
这是我们在他人间蒸发之前
It's the only chance we have of finding him before
-找到他的唯一机会  -我去
He disappears forever. i'll do it.
你要保证她的安全  听见了吗
You keep her safe, you hear me?
一定
We will.
上校
Colonel!
联调局
Fbi.
快走
Go! go!
我要和你勾结的所有
I want the names of everyone in the united states government
美国政府的官员名单
That you've been working with.
我有份名单
I have a list.
我找到了一个植入杜巴库皮肤里的
I found some kind of digital storage device
数码存储设备
Implanted under dubaku's skin.
能把文件上传到联调局吗
Can you upload the files to fbi?
玛丽卡死了
Marika didn't make it.
-你害死了我妹妹  -我很抱歉
- You killed my sister. - I'm so sorry.
你究竟想干吗
What do you want from me?!
我只想知道你还有点人味儿
I just want to know that you feel something
我想知道你和我有同样的切肤之痛
I want to know that you feel the same kind of pain as i do.
感觉到了吗
Do you feel that?!
我和联调局合作
I'm working with fbi
协助进行内部地毯式搜捕
To coordinate an interagency sweep.
我们应该在一小时之内开始实施逮捕
We should start making arrests within the hour.
对于今天你的付出   我们会没齿难忘
What you have done here today puts all of us in your debt.
要谢的人很多
There are a lot of people to thank,
包括杰克·鲍尔
Including jack bauer.
需要我做什么  比尔
What are you asking me to do, bill?
我要你告诉参议员迈尔
I'm asking you to speak to senator mayer.
杰克·鲍尔协助我们拯救了这个国家
Jack bauer helped save this country.
他不该在监狱里度过余生
He doesn't deserve to spend the rest of his life in prison.
-我要去白宫  -什么
- I'm going to the white house. - Sir?
泰勒总统想跟我讨论杰克·鲍尔的事情
President taylor wants to speak to me regarding jack bauer.
带上你的手提电脑  莱恩
Grab your laptop, ryan.
你得跟我一起去
I want you there with me.
还会有另一次袭击
There's gonna be another attack.
就在华盛顿
Here in d.c.
我的线人告诉我
My source tells me
行动时间是晚上7点
That the window opens at 1900 hours.
目标是什么
What's the target?
他不清楚具体目标
He doesn't know the exact target,
但肯定是袭击价值高
But it's definitely going to be of high value
能造成巨大影响的东西
And high impact.
他提供给我一个人名
He gave me the name of somebody
-此人跟这个计划有关系  -谁
- Who's been involved in the planning. - Who?
瑞恩·伯内特
Ryan burnett.
参议院迈尔的办公室主任
Senator mayer's chief of staff.
对
That's right.
[人马到位  准备行动]
Units in place. Operation on schedule.
以下事件发生在下午6点到7点
The following takes place between 6 p.m. and 7 p.m.
稍等
Hold on a second.
走吧
Go ahead.
重症监护室
Icu.
请稍等
One moment, please.
科琳娜  三号线有你的电话
Corinna, you got a call on three.
谁
Who is it?
梅医生  他有事问你
Dr. may. he's got a question.
医生真是没用
Doctors are so helpless.
梅医生
Dr. may?
喂
Hello?
没人啊
There was no one there.
要是他打过来
If he calls back, tell him
跟他说我稍后给他打回去
I'll call him back in a minute.
紧急呼救
Code blue.
紧急呼救  重症监护室有紧急情况
Code blue! we have a code blue in the icu!
叫沃克探员马上赶到重症监护室
Get agent walker down to icu now!
迅速果断是五角大楼对此次正在
Swift and decisive is how the pentagon describes
进军桑加拉行动的描述
The u.s. invasion now underway in sangala.
零星的抵抗  最小的伤亡
"sporadic resistance, minimal casualties."
这直接与桑加拉领导人
This in direct contrast to assertions made
本杰明·朱玛在国家电视台
By sangalese leader benjamin juma
做出的断言形成鲜明对比
On state-supported television.
我们勇敢的士兵将击退
Our brave soldiers are beating back the enemy
所有入侵桑加拉的军队
All across sangala city.
历史将由我们谱写  我的朋友
History is on our side, my friends.
曾经我们能在美国佬的贩奴船上生还
We survived their slave ships,
今天也同样能在他们船坚炮利下幸存
And we will survive their warships, too.
当自己的部队弃城而逃  城市一片废墟时
Declaring victory while his own troops are fleeing the capital,
他还在这儿宣扬胜利
And his palace lies in ruins.
这个视频是什么时候录的
When do we think this was made?
我估计视频是在
My guess is these recordings were made
我们进攻之前录制的  总统阁下
Some time before the invasion, ma'am.
问题来了  约翰
Which begs the question, john.
他现在在哪  为什么我现在还抓不到他
Where is he, and why haven't we found him yet?
特种部队正在桑加拉展开全城搜捕
Special forces teams all over sangala city
搜寻他的藏身之处
Are searching for him.
有情报称
There is some intelligence to suggest
他可能已经逃离国内了
He may have fled the country.
史密斯上将
Admiral smith, you and i
你我都清楚必须抓到朱玛
Both know that juma must be captured.
我们必须要对他侵犯人权的罪恶行径
He must be tried and convicted
进行审判和定罪
of his crimes against humanity
否则  我们一样很失败
Otherwise, we've as good as failed.
他跑不远的  总统阁下
He can't go far, ma'am.
世界上没有一个国家会给他提供政治庇护
No country on earth will grant him asylum.
那就抓住他  史密斯上将
Then find him, admiral smith.
无论天涯海角
Wherever he is.
朱玛将军
General juma?
景色迷人  不是吗
Beautiful, isn't it?
什么
Sir?
我可不是跟你闹着玩  劳伦特
It's not a trick question, laurent.
真的很迷人
It is beautiful.
不是吗
Why not?
时间快到了
It is almost time.
弟兄们  他们都准备好了吗
The men-- are they ready?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
他们害怕吗
Are they afraid?
我不知道  但是有些人在祈祷
I don't know, sir, but some of them are praying.
害怕是好事
It's good if they are afraid.
意味着他们会奋勇杀敌
It means they will fight bravely.
长官  你有我父亲的消息吗
Have you heard from my father yet, sir?
我以为他会在这儿跟我们会面的
I thought he was supposed to be meeting us here.
别担心  劳伦特
Don't worry, laurent.
他会来的
He will be here.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
什么事
Yes.
-杜巴库上校死了  -你确定吗
Colonel dubaku is dead. Are you certain?
我用的药可是致命的
The dose i administered was catastrophic.
他儿子刚才还问我呢
His son just asked me about him.
永远不要让他知道这事
He must never know about this,
还有他父亲是个懦夫
Or about his father's cowardice.
他不会知道的
He won't.
那就没什么能妨碍咱们了
Then nothing will stand in our way,
乌铎  但是要抓紧
udo. but hurry.
攻击行动时间快到了
The attack window is narrowing.
时间必须精确
The timing must be precise.
-退后  -明白  长官
- Clear! - yes, sir.
退后
Clear.
再来一次  360伏
One more time at 360.
退后
Clear.
不行
Nothing.
再来一次吗  医生
Going again, doctor?
不用了
No.
就这样了  各位  宣布死亡
That's it, everybody. i'm calling it.
死亡时间  下午6点
time death 06 p.m.
斯塔尔医生  怎么回事
Dr. stahl, what's going on?
严重的心脏病发作
A massive heart attack.
你说过他情况稳定就会好转
You said that he was stable, that he was going to be okay.
这又是怎么了
So, what happened?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
可能有些没预料到的情况
Maybe a preexisting condition.
验尸报告会说明一切  失陪
The autopsy will tell us. Excuse me.
大规模腐败稽查
The wide extent of the corruption
需要联合行动
requires a coordinated approach.
政府已经被渗透
We know the government's been compromised.
但我们还不知道有多少内鬼
We just don't know at what level.
现在  克罗伊·奥布赖恩正在逐个部门
Presently, Chloe O'brian is vetting the names
审查名单
Department by department.
我已经予以特勤局优先权
I'm prioritizing secret service,
总统的安全将很快得到保障
so the president is secured as soon as possible.
各部负责人会接到指令
Team leaders will then receive their assignments--
包括国防部  财政部  国务院等等
defense, treasury, state,et cetera and make
在整个华府地区同时实施抓捕
their arrests contemporaneously across the district.
-我是奥布赖恩  -克罗伊  我是杰克
O'brian. Chloe, it's Jack.
杜巴库数据库里的名单传给
Have the names from Dubaku's database been handed over
逮捕小组了没
to the arrest teams yet?
-还没  -好  听我说
- Not yet. - Okay, listen to me.
我刚刚得知朱玛团伙正在计划新一轮攻击
I've just learned that Juma's operatives are planning another attack.
杰克  他们说这一切就要结束了
Jack, they're telling us here it's over.
不对  托尼给我提供了情报来源
That's wrong. Tony's my source on the intel.
你知道他们的目标吗
Do you know what the target is?
只知道那是代价高  伤亡大的地方
Only that it's high value, high casualty, and that
危机正在酝酿中  所以我需要你帮我
it's happening now, which is why I need your help.
名单上有个叫莱恩·伯内特的
There's a man on the list, a Ryan Burnett.
他是迈尔议员的办公室主任
He's Senator Mayer's Chief of Staff.
迈尔  他不就是今早在参议院小组听证会上
Mayer? Isn't he the guy who grilled you this morning
盘问你的那个人吗
at the senate subcommittee hearing?
没错  但他不是同谋
Yeah, but the Senator's not implicated in the conspiracy.
不过伯内特一直在
But Burnett has been providing support
支持朱玛和杜巴库
for Juma and Dubaku all along.
克罗伊  我要你从名单里删掉他的名字
Chloe, I need you to delete his name from the list.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
一旦调查局对他下手  他的律师就会赶到
If the FBI start to move in on him, he'll lawyer up,
这样一来没人能及时得知任何情报
and no one will get the information on time.
他现在在哪
Where is he now?
他和参议员一起在白宫
He's at the white house with the Senator.
他们要和总统会面
They've got a meeting with the president.
我正去那儿  准备盘问比尔
I'm on my way there now to be debriefed by Bill.
我会搞定他的
I'll take care of him then.
杰克  你不会是想在白宫审嫌犯吧
Jack, you don't expect to interrogate a suspect in the white house?
交给我了
Let me handle that.
克罗伊  删掉他的名字
Chloe, just get his name deleted from the list.
我会再打给你的
I'll get back to you.
她也入伙了
She's in.
-有进展吗  -快了
- How close are we? -Close.
有什么我能帮忙的吗
Is there anything I can do to help?
我正在浏览资料的最后一页
I'm just cycling through the last layer of data now.
你看  要是你把分组完毕的资料
You know, it might be quicker
一个个发到我的工作台可能会快点
if you send the subsets to my station one by one.
好主意
Good idea.
之后
And then that way
我就可以分发它们了
I can get to work on distributing them.
-好吧  -多谢
Okay, then. Thank you.
听着  杰克  你得再考虑一下
Listen, Jack, maybe you should reconsider.
考虑什么
Reconsider what?
相信比尔
Taking Bill into your confidence.
我是说  他从一开始
Look, I mean, he's been a part
就一直在参与这次行动
of this operation since the get-go.
我不知道得用啥手段才能撬开伯内特的嘴
I don't know what it's going to take to get Burnett to talk.
如果我必须用极端手法的话
If I have to use extreme measures...
我不明白  你怎就觉得他一定会去那儿呢
I don't get it. What, you don't think he'll go there?
我正一步步走向悬崖  托尼
I'm driving off a cliff here, Tony.
我没必要把比尔也拉下水
I don't need to put Bill in the passenger seat.
好吧  我会和你去
All right, then, fine. I'll go with you.
你是个被通缉的重犯
You're a wanted felon.
你连第一道安检都过不去
You wouldn't get past the first checkpoint.
除此之外  现在所有政府部门
Besides, with all of the government agencies
仍旧被渗透  也许可以靠你自己
still compromised, it might be up to you
阻止这次袭击
to stop the attack.
永别了
See you on the other side.
喂
Yes?
能延长袭击的行动时间吗
Can you extend the attack window?
那可能会影响整个计划
Not without risking the entire operation.
干嘛
Why?
事情有点棘手了
There's been a complication.
我不能按预计的那样按时动身了
I may be stuck here longer than I anticipated.
我会再打给你的
I'll call you back.
卡宁先生
Mr. Kanin.
我是莱恩·伯内特  迈尔议员的办公室主任
Ryan Burnett, Senator Mayer's Chief of Staff.
-我们通过电话  -不止一次
- We've spoken on the phone. - Many times.
见到你真好
It's good to finally meet you.
我也是  参议员在里面
Likewise. The Senator's inside.
跟我来
Right this way.
参议员
Senator?
参议员  在喝酒啊
Well, Senator, I see you've found the bar.
我也来一杯好吗
Mind if I join you?
这酒我还没见过
Something I never knew.
不是肯塔基州来的就不能算是波旁威士忌
If it ain't from Kentucky, you can't call it Bourbon.
伊桑  少跟我来你南方佬那一套
Spare me the southern gentleman routine, Ethan.
总统让我在这个天杀的傍晚
The president didn't call me up here
来这儿可不是一边喝酒一边
at the ass-end of the day to drink her booze
浏览一个简报
and flip through a briefing book.
在会前这可能会对你有帮助
I thought it might be helpful, before your meeting,
让你能了解
to bring you up to speed
最近十小时发生的事情
on the events of the last ten hours.
好吧
Okay.
我已经了解了
I'm up to speed.
参议员  你一定对你刚才
Senator, surely you have some reaction
读到的东西有些感想吧
to what you just read.
我当然有
Damn right I have a reaction.
我想知道这一切和杰克·鲍尔有何瓜葛
I want to know what all this has to do with Jack Bauer.
这也是我来此的原因  对吗
I mean, that's the reason I'm here, right?
没有鲍尔先生  我们不可能
Without Mr. Bauer, we would never have uncovered
首先揭穿阴谋
the conspiracy in the first place
更不可能找到幕后主使
nor the people behind it.
正是有了他与联调局合力联手
His efforts, in conjunction
才促成了现在
with those of the FBI, are largely responsible
正在进行的华府内的大搜捕
for the arrests being made right now across the district.
你不会是说他是奉旨办事吧
You're not saying that he's acting in an official capacity?
我不用告诉你这意味着什么吧  伊桑
I don't have to tell you how this looks, Ethan.
与解散的前反恐组流氓探员狼狈为奸
Colluding with a rogue operative from a disbanded agency.
很遗憾你这么看问题
I'm sorry you see it that way.
我还能怎么看这个问题
How else am I supposed to see it?
依照总统的看法
The way the president does--
杰克·鲍尔救百姓于水火  这显而易见
that Jack Bauer saved lives today, plain and simple,
其中也包括救了她丈夫
including her husband's.
我知道  参议员  这对你来说很难接受
Look, Senator, I know this isn't easy for you.
你发起的反对
The public battle you've waged
被拘留人员受虐以及违背人权的斗争
against detainee abuse and human rights violations...
你是郑重要求我
Are you seriously asking me
改变立场吗
to look the other way on this?
我追查这个混蛋好些年了
I have been after this son of a bitch for years.
他是个恶棍  伊桑
He's a thug, Ethan.
他是头号公敌
He's exhibit "a."
总统已经准备好改变政策
The president is prepared to reverse policy
支持你关于战争犯罪的修正案
and support your amendment to the war crimes act.
交换条件是什么
In exchange for what exactly?
听证会
The hearings.
宣布休会至假期后
Declare a recess till after the holidays
接着悄悄等鲍尔先生的传票作废
And then quietly let Mr. Bauer's subpoena expire.
要是我拒绝合作呢
And if I refuse to go along?
总统也做好了
The president is prepared
使用行政特权的准备
to invoke executive privilege.
行政特权具体指什么
Executive privilege--meaning what exactly?
那就由总统决定了
Well,that's for the president to decide.
你是说赦免吗
Are you talking about a pardon?
不排除这种可能
I wouldn't rule it out.
如果总统想耍花样
Well, if that's how the president wants to play it,
你可以告诉她她遇到对手了
You can tell her she just walked into a street fight.
你可以自己跟她说
You can tell her yourself.
杰克
Jack.
-你好比尔  -你比我预期的来得早
Hi, bill. you got here sooner than i expected.
-杰克 -放下武器
- Jack. - Put down your weapon now!
离桌子远点
Step away from the desk!
坐下
Take a seat.
比尔  坐下
Sit down, bill!
好  好  我坐下了
Okay, okay, i'm sitting.
到底发生了什么事
Now, what's this all about?
莱恩·伯内特在哪
Where is ryan burnett? what?
参议员的办公室主任  他在哪
Senator mayer's chief of staff-- where is he?
我不会说的
I'm not saying anything until you tell me
除非你告诉我到底发生了什么事
What the hell's going on.
托尼从他的线人口中
Tony doubled back to one of his contacts,
知道有第二次袭击
Who gave him information of a second attack.
一个小时内会在华盛顿发动袭击
It's going to take place here in washington within the hour.
这次是朱玛的手下
Juma's operatives are carrying it out.
伯内特一直在暗中支持他们
Burnett's been supporting them all along.
他知道下一次袭击会在哪里发生
He knows where the attack's going to take place, so you can
你如果不说出他的下落  我会自己找
Either tell me where he is or i will find him myself.
我不能说  杰克
Jack, I can't.
手放背后
Fine, put your hands behind your back now.
情报准确吗
How good is the intel?
这情报值得我找他谈谈的了
Good enough for me to need to talk to him.
不要动
Don't you move.
杰克  让我逮捕他吧
Jack, let me have him arrested.
我们还可以想想别的办法
There are other ways to deal with this.
袭击已经破在眉睫  我们没时间了
The attack window's open. We're out of time.
杰克  听我说
Jack, listen to me.
我为你的事情和总统谈过了
I spoke to the president on your behalf.
她会和迈尔参议员谈
She's going to intervene with senator mayer,
关于停止你的听证会的事
Stop the hearings.
你可以重获新生了
You can get your life back.
你现在这么做等于自毁前程啊
You do this, you're throwing it all away.
我希望还有另一种选择
I wish I thought there was another option.
至少让我帮你  杰克
Let me help you at least, jack.
你不用一个人面对
You don't have to do this alone.
是的  我必须一个人
Yes, i do.
这是唯一一个能不让你受到牵连的方法
It's the only way i can make sure to keep you Out of this.
-杰克 -比尔  对不起
- Jack. - Bill, i'm sorry.
杰克  等  等一下
Jack, w-w-wait!
杰克
Jack!
没事的
It's all right.
不要反抗了
Don't fight it.
我是莫斯
This is Moss.
拉里  是我
Larry, it's me.
杜巴库死了
Dubaku's dead.
医生不是说他已经稳定下来了吗
I thought the doctors said he was stabilized.
发生什么事了
What happened?
医院方面说
Officially,
他死于冠状动脉
They're characterizing that it was a coronary
破裂引起的系统性休克
Brought on by systemic shock.
好像你并不相信啊
Sounds like you don't believe it.
我和医院主管部门确认了一下
I did a follow-up with the hospital admin.
她确定杜巴库死的时候
She confirmed that there was an eight-member team on duty
有一个八人组在值班
When dubaku flatlined.
然后呢
Yeah?
在重症病房里有第九个人
There was a ninth man in the icu
正巧在急救信号之前出现  是个护理人员
Just before the code was called-- an orderly.
我重新看了一下监护室的录像带
I ran back the tapes on the ward
发现了那第九个人
And that's when i spotted him.
关键是周围没人知道他是谁
The things is I've asked around and nobody seems to know who he is.
蕾妮  你是在说杜巴库是被人谋杀的吗
Renee, wait, a-are you saying you think dubaku was murdered?
我是说杜巴库心跳停止的时候
I'm saying that there was an unidentified man in with dubaku
一个不明身份的人却在他旁边
Just before he went into cardiac arrest.
医院主管怎么说
What does the admin say?
他说他们经常从其他地区医院
She says that they often use floaters-- Personnel from other area hospitals
借用临时工
Filling in from time to time.
他们认为正式员工不认识他
Said it's not uncommon for the regular staff
也没什么奇怪的
Not to know who they are.
她在复审员工名单
She's double-checking with payroll now.
这样不就有答案了吗
Right, so there's your answer.
我还是觉得不对劲
Still it seems odd.
我是说  万一杜巴库知道些什么
I mean, what if dubaku knew something
所以招来杀身之祸
And they needed to shut him up?
这又是鲍尔的理论对吧
Is this bauer's theory, too?
他甚至都不在这
Jack's not even here
拉里  我讨厌你这么妄加猜疑
And, you know, I resent that implication, larry.
我没说什么呀
What implication is that?
你的意思就是说我是个傀儡了
I am not the one calling the shots.
这从一开始就是我的案子
This has been my investigation from the beginning,
不是杰克·鲍尔的
Not jack bauer's.
我就是问问而已
I was just asking a question.
代表不了什么
I wasn't implying anything.
-你在吗  -对不起
- You there? - I'm sorry.
我对这件事有点敏感
I guess i'm a little sensitive on the subject.
我们已经了解了杜巴库所知道的一切
Look, everything we needed from dubaku, we got.
所有被他收买的政府官员名字和银行帐户
Names and bank accounts Of every corrupt official on his payroll.
现在正把他们缉拿归案呢
Teams are in the field as we speak.
你是说你让我回去吗
So you're saying you want me to come in.
我们这边需要你的帮助逮捕那些犯人
We need you back in the office sooner than later
越早越好
To help process all these arrests.
拉里  我让保安搜查了整个医院
Larry, look, I've got security searching the hospital
并检查了大量监控录像
And reviewing more video.
你要继续追那条线索吗
So, what, you want to follow that up first?
好吧  查明之后向我回报
Fine, call me when you clear it. yeah.
我会的
I will.
拉里  谢谢
Thanks, larry.
打扰一下  沃克探员
Excuse me, agent walker?
我们停车场的监视器
That orderly you were looking for
拍到了你要找的那个护理人员
One of our parking lot cameras
-上车时的画面  -什么时候
- Picked him up getting into his car. - When?
大概15分钟之前
Uh, about 15 minutes ago. i've got a screen grab
有一个探头拍下了他的车牌号
Of his license plate.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是沃克探员
This is agent walker.
帮我接下汽车管理局
Put me through to our DMV contact.
你在忙吗
Are you busy?
我正在重置服务器
I'm just reformatting the server,
所以比较忙  有事吗
So, yeah, I guess I am busy. why?
我在比对杜巴库提供的海外帐户
Well, I was cross-referencing Dubaku's offshore accounts
我查到一个残留标题信息
And i came across an orphaned header fragment.
你在说些什么
What are you talking about?
你看一下
Take a look.
看见了吗  就在那  在那
Okay, see, there, right there, right there.
一个残留的标题
It's a remnant file header.
有可能那只是一个虚拟数据串而已
It's probably just a phantom data string.
不是的
No, it isn't.
我做过系统分析
I ran a systems analysis.
编码不是随机的
The coding is not random.
可以通过它
It can be traced back
追踪到一个帐户
To one of the accounts.
也就是说一个名字
Also, it looks like a name was deleted
被人从名单上删除了
From the list.
我来修复它吧
Why don't I run a recovery program?
你正在忙着重置系统
Well, you're very busy with the reformatting and all,
让我上传到我的工作站那边修复吧
So why don't I just upload it to my station and take care of it there?
不碍事  我这比较快
Well, that's okay, i can do it faster.
恕我冒犯
No offense.
我恢复资料的时候会通知你的
I'll let you know if I retrieve anything.
好吧
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
Thank you.
请讲
Yeah.
你抓到伯内特了吗
Have you gotten to Burnett yet?
还没有
Working on it.
正在去白宫的路上
Making my way over to the west wing.
这有人发现
Someone here has figured out
数据库中少了一个名字
That a name has been deleted from the database.
我不知道还能稳住她多久
I don't know how much longer i can hold her off.
他们知道是伯内特吗
Do they know it was burnett?
不  可这只是时间问题
No, but it's just a matter of time.
好  我回头找你
Okay, i'll get back to you.
好
Great.
参议员  我要回一趟国会找桑迪
Senator, i'll head back to the hill and get with sandy.
你开完会前
We should have a press release drafted
得先起草完一份新闻发布稿
By the time you finish your meeting.
我还准备和你的朋友豪瑟面谈
I'm also going to need a sit-down with your friend hauser at the post.
不要声张   对吧
Off the record, i assume.
我们得把赦免杰克的行为视作
We've got to make pardoning jack bauer as politically toxic
危害总统的政治毒瘤
For the president as possible.
她现在很情绪化
She's a woman in a highly emotional state.
她丈夫刚被枪击
Her husband's been shot.
你是说她判断力也会受影响吗
You suggesting her judgment's impaired?
我建议我们可以就此弹劾总统了
I'm suggesting that a case could be made.
打搅一下  参议员
Excuse me, senator.
泰勒总统有请
President taylor is ready to see you now.
去吧  参议员
Go ahead, senator.
我会把这带给司法部长
I'll get this to the ag,
告诉他你选择继续
Tell him you want the option to go ahead
明天按原计划参加听证会
With the hearings tomorrow as scheduled.
谢谢  莱恩
Thanks, ryan.
喂
Yes?
我是伯内特
It's burnett.
你解决后患了吗
You took care of the problem?
我要走了
I'm leaving now.
计划照常  我们晚上九点半会面
Good, then we rendezvous at 2130 hours, as planned.
好
I'll be there.
抱歉  我这就过去
Excuse me, i'll be out of here
马上
In just one second.
我和你...
You and i...
我们得谈谈
...we're going to have a talk.
我们在旧行政办公楼设立了一个指挥所
We've got a command post set up at EEOB,
我们会向中情局和外交安全局汇报
And we'll brief cia and diplomatic security,
不过这得等我们执行完第一次地毯式搜捕后
But not until after the first sweep of arrests.
听着  没人跑得了
Look, nobody is going anywhere, phil.
我们已经在城内布下了天罗地网
We've dropped a net on the city.
有情况我会即时通知你
And i'll let you know as soon as that happens.
好
All right.
抱歉打扰
Yeah. i'm sorry to interrupt,
可你得听些东西
But i need you to listen to something.
-我可以吗  -没事
- May i? - Yeah, that's fine.
她应该是一流的系统分析员
She's supposed to be this whiz-bang systems analyst,
首先提醒我的是
Which is actually what tipped me off in the first place.
她的行为很怪异
Her demeanor is so bizarre...
詹尼斯
w-w-whoa, janis,
你在说谁
Who are you talking about?
克罗伊·奥布赖恩
Chloe o'brian.
我检查了她的系统  结果发现
I ran a systems check on her work, and it turns out
有她篡改资料的证据
There's evidence of file tampering.
加上所有被她加密过的外线电话
Plus she's been scrambling all her out-of-office phone call
所以我注意了一下她的
So i had operations archive
往来通讯记录
Her cellular traffic.
我破解处理了一下
I did a work-around.
听
Listen.
喂
Yeah.
你找到伯内特了吗
Have you gotten to burnett yet?
正在找
Working on it.
我正前往白宫
Making my way over to the west wing.
我们这里有人已经发现
Someone here has figured out
数据库上已经删除了一个人名
That a name has been deleted from the database.
我不知道还能稳住她多久
I don't know how much longer i can hold her off.
他们知道是伯内特的名字吗
Do they know it was burnett?
不知道  但迟早会发现
No, but it's just a matter of time.
好  回头联系你
Okay, i'll get back to you.
贝克
Becker.
去会议室
In the conference room.
我要你扣留克罗伊·奥布赖恩
I want chloe o'brian detained.
-让她退出那个服务器  -遵命
And get her off that server. Yes.
奥布莱恩女士   请跟我走一趟
Mrs. O'Brian?  You need to come with me.
帮我接白宫
Get me the white house.
总统阁下  我只想提醒您
Let me just remind you, madam president,
您支持的行为
You supported the effort
是为了禁止虐待和拷问
To ban abuse and torture.
您参加竞选是为了改革情报部门
You campaigned to reform the intelligence agencies.
参议员  过去的这十小时
These past ten hours, senator,
是非黑白没那么容易辨别
Things haven't appeared as black and white as they once did.
杰克·鲍尔没那么有神秘色彩
Well, there's nothing gray about jack bauer.
他对人施暴
The man has committed atrocities.
在他的羁押下囚犯都死去了
Prisoners have died in his custody.
鲍尔先生得到过三任总统的信任和支持
Mr. bauer has served under the aegis
不止我一个人如此
Of three presidents, not just me.
如果这是被授予最高级别待遇的话
Is it any more lawful or any less repugnant
是否就更合法或不再那么令人讨厌了呢
If it's authorized at the highest level?
对于任何一任总统来说
A state of war is not a blank check
国家战争都得付出昂贵代价
For the president or for anyone.
别对我说教  参议员
Oh, don't lecture me, senator.
我很清楚自己权力有限
I am well aware of the limits of my power.
恕我直言  总统阁下
Due respect, madam president...
你权力很大
Your power is great.
还是谨慎些为好
Just be careful
确保自己利用它发出了正确的信号
That you use it to send the right message.
我只想让你
All i'm asking you to do
赦免杰克·鲍尔
Is excuse mr. bauer as a witness.
这不是个信号
It's not a message.
而是我对于他今天的贡献表示感激的方式
It is an expression of gratitude for what he's done today.
你让我赦免他
You're asking me to excuse him
让他不至于成为众矢之的调查对象
As a target of the investigation.
信号已经传达得很清楚了
And the message is clear.
有些情况下
Under certain circumstances,
您相信他的做法可行
You believe his methods are acceptable.
有些人也觉得可行
Some would argue that they are.
可他们错了
And they would be wrong.
无论用何种军事或者道德标准
Under any military or moral standard.
美国走过冤枉路的  总统阁下
America has been down this road before, madam president.
你自己将其称之为国难
You yourself called it a national tragedy.
确实是国难
It was a tragedy.
我仍然坚信这点
I still believe that.
赦免杰克·鲍尔
Pardon jack bauer,
你就是在对这行的每个刑讯逼供的人说
And you're telling every interrogator in the field
大家放手虐囚吧  百无禁忌咯
That it's open season again.
抱歉打断您  总统阁下
I'm sorry to interrupt, madam president.
联调局的拉里·莫斯的急电
There's an urgent call from larry moss at fbi.
接进来
Put him through.
莫斯探员在线上
Agent moss is on the line.
莫斯探员
Agent moss,
我是伊森·卡宁
This is ethan kanin.
你正和总统连线
You're on speaker with the president.
总统阁下  请原谅我
Madam president, forgive me for
冒然来电
coming directly
您今晚要和迈尔参议员见面吗
You have a meeting this evening with senator mayer?
事实上  的确如此
In fact, i do.
我正和他在一起
I'm with him right now.
参议员的办公室主任  莱恩·伯内特
Did the senator's Chief of staff, ryan burnett, accompany
陪同参议员来白宫了吗
The senator to the white house?
来了  莫斯探员  怎么了
Yes, he did, agent moss-- why?
我有理由相信杰克·鲍尔
I have reason to believe that jack bauer
正在非法审讯伯内特先生
Is carrying out an off-book interrogation of mr. burnett
就在我们通话的当口
As we speak.
电池耗尽前
I can pull the trigger
我足以扣动128次扳机  甚至更多
128 more times before this battery dies.
告诉你
I'm telling you,
我对攻击一点都不知情
I don't know anything about an attack.
别对我撒谎
Stop lying to me.
-我没撒谎  -目标是哪里
- I'm not lying. - What's the target?
-我没法告诉你我不知道的事  -伯内特先生
- I can't tell you what i don't know. - Mr. burnett,
你是个叛国者  一个恐怖分子
You are a traitor and a terrorist.
我不是
I'm not.
我爱我的祖国
I love my country.
这是1200伏特的电流
That was 1,200 volts of current.
现在当我把这个盒子拿出来的时候
Now, when i eject this cartridge,
我会启动超频晕眩模式
I access the drive stun mode,
一旦启动  电压会猛增到40倍
Upping the voltage 40 times When directly administered.
你只要老实交代就成
All you need to do is talk to me.
伯内特先生  真的很简单
Mr. burnett, it's really simple.
只要告诉我  袭击目标是什么
Just tell me what the target is,
-这一切就结束了  -我向你保证
-And this will be all over. -i promise.
我真的不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
-这是你最后一次机会  -如果我知道
-This is your last chance. -if i knew,
我肯定会告诉你的  我发誓
I would tell you, i swear it.
你要我说什么呢
What do you want me to say?
你告诉我该怎么说  然后我重复一遍
Just... just tell me what to say, and i'll say it.
跟我玩鬼把戏  想都别想
Don't you even try and play that game with me.
伯内特先生  这行我干了很久了
Mr. burnett, i've been doing this a long time,
一个人在被胁迫的时候
And i can tell the difference,
他那到底有没有我要的情报
Especially when a man is under duress,
还是纯粹在浪费我的时间
If he's got information that i need
我能判断出来的
Or if i'm just wasting my time.
这次我向你保证  我没有浪费时间
And i promise you, i am not wasting my time.
下一轮
The next jolt
咱整整你的咽喉
Is gonna be in your throat.
你颈部以上所有的器官
Anything above your neck runs the risk
都会面临肌肉神经停滞的危险
Of a complete neuromuscular shutdown.
这就是说  你有可能瘫痪
That means you run the risk of becoming paralyzed.
求你不要
No, please.
伯内特先生  你一手安排了整个听证会
Mr. burnett, you built the entire federal case
就是为了针对我
Against me.
你们都应该知道  为了阻止这次恐怖袭击
You of all people should know how far i am willing to go
我会不择手段
To stop this attack from happening.
我再问你最后一次
So, i'm gonna ask you one last time.
恐怖袭击的目标是什么
Where is the target?!
我
I...
我说  我说  我说
Okay, okay, okay.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
有士兵
Soldiers.
多少人
How many?
一个小队
A unit.
朱玛的总统卫队
Juma's presidential guard.
什么时候
When?
已经开始了
It already started.
目标是哪
Where?
是哪
Where?!
鲍尔先生
Mr. bauer,
我是总统泰勒
This is president taylor.
目标是哪
Where is the target?
-鲍尔先生  -目标是哪
Mr. bauer... where?!
鲍尔先生  我命令你接电话
Mr. bauer, i am ordering you to answer this page.
鲍尔先生  你听到没
Mr. bauer, do you hear me?
见鬼
Damn it!
总统阁下  我是杰克·鲍尔
Madam president, this is jack bauer.
我不知道你现在了解到多少情况了
I don't know what you've heard so far,
但是这件事情  还没完
But this thing is not over.
几分钟之内  还会有
There is another terrorist attack
新的恐怖袭击发生
Going to take place within minutes.
不给我开门  就不谈这些
There will be no discussion until you unlock this door.
总统阁下  袭击已经开始了
Madam president, the attack window is open.
朱玛的人已经行动了
Juma's men are moving.
鲍尔先生  你这样做是违法的
What you're doing is against the law, mr. bauer.
我是总司令官  我命令你
I am your commander in chief, and i am ordering you
停止行动
To stand down.
还要多长时间  警卫
How much longer, sergeant?
-已经可以了  阁下  -动手
-Good to go, ma'am. -do it.
目标在哪
Where's the target?
Where is the target?!
目标...
Where is...?!
我逼他说了
I had him!
有人受伤
Man down.
急诊队快来贵宾接待室
Emts to the visiting dignitary suite.
你完了  鲍尔
You're done, bauer.
你没戏了
You're finished.
他就要招了
He was talking.
不论发生什么  现在已经在发生了
Whatever's going to happen is happening now,
你等着遭良心谴责吧
And it's on your conscience.
我的良心比起你的来  问题少得多
My conscience has a lot less to answer for than yours.
鲍尔先生  你说有袭击会发生
Mr. bauer, you say an attack is imminent.
我的情报来源很可靠
My source intel is good.
谁是你的情报来源
Who is your source?
这个我不想说
I'd rather not say.
名字  鲍尔先生
The name, mr. bauer.
托尼·阿尔梅达
Tony almeida.
托尼·阿尔梅达  他是个逃犯
Tony almeida-- the man's a fugitive.
没有他  我们是不会
Without tony almeida, we would never
重获CIP装置的
Have recovered the cip device.
总统阁下
Madam president,
我不管  就算他的情报来源
I don't care if his source
是圣母玛利亚
Is the blessed virgin mary.
也不能为他刚在这房间里的所作所为开脱
Nothing justifies what went on in this room.
即使他是正确的吗  布莱恩
Even if he's right, blaine?
即使这样做能拯救很多生命吗
Even if it means we could save lives?
看看吧  这不就是野蛮吗
Look at that, and tell me it's not barbarism.
你能眼睁睁看着这些事情发生吗
Is that something you can live with?
今天早些时候  总统阁下
Earlier today, madam president,
两架飞机相撞
Two airplanes were brought down.
你能眼睁睁看着这些事情发生吗
Is that something you can live with?
你是应受谴责  鲍尔
You're reprehensible, bauer.
而长官你太软弱
and you, sir, are weak!
对邪恶的事情
Unwilling and unable
不想也无力去跟他们针锋相对
To look evil in the eye and deal with it.
伊桑  借一步说话
Ethan, step out for a second.
突然之间  这就不算假设了  对不对
Suddenly, it's not so hypothetical, is it?
在你看来
In your opinion,
鲍尔的情报  可信吗
Is bauer's intelligence actionable?
如果鲍尔说会有恐怖袭击
If bauer says there's going to be an attack,
我是相信的
My belief is, there's going to be an attack.
拷打最初被认为是刑讯逼供的手段
Torture was originally intended to force false confessions.
现在我们却用它来寻求真相
Now we use it to try and find the truth.
这些人谋害了您的儿子  总统阁下
These people murdered your son, madam president.
又差点谋杀了您的丈夫
They attempted to murder your husband.
他们已经肆无忌惮
They will stop at nothing.
警卫  把鲍尔先生带走
Sergeant, take mr. bauer away.
他被捕了
He's under arrest.
你应该先来找我的
You should have come to me.
你应该报案的
You should have presented your case.
没时间的
We didn't have time.
就算报告给您  又有什么不同呢  阁下
And would it really have made a difference, ma'am?
总统阁下
Madam president...
你做的是对的
You're doing the right thing.
已经死了271个人了
271 dead already.
我向上帝祈祷  我做的是对的
I wish to god it felt more like the right thing.
伊桑  提高恐怖袭击的预警等级
Ethan, raise the threat levels.
通告国土安全局
Tell homeland that they have
他们得马上制定一个应急方案
To come up with a response scenario.
还有  把蒂姆叫过来
And get tim down here.
并且  我要跟伯内特亲自谈一下
Also, i want to talk to mr. burnett myself.
我去跟他谈吧
Let me do that.
我了解他
I know the man.
很显然  你并不了解
Apparently, you don't.
蒂姆  我知道恐怖袭击预警已经提高
Tim, i understand the threat level
但是只针对些快速反应机构和联邦机构
Has been raised, but only for first responders and federal agents.
有件事需要关注  恐怖袭击发生的时候
There's a concern that mass evacuation
大规模的疏散群众
By the public could hamper efforts
可能会影响我们拖延恐怖袭击的效率
To thwart an attack when it comes.
华盛顿的空域怎么样
What about the airspace over washington?
已经限飞
Restricted.
已经开始着手组织军机低空巡逻
Military flyovers are commencing.
国防部建议我们部署机动部队
DOD has recommended that we deploy mobile teams to sweep the area
彻底搜查附近的放射性和生物性物质
For radioactive and biological signatures.
我马上打电话给五角大楼的菲利浦
I'll call phillip at the pentagon
让他赶快行动
and push it through.
国安局那边呢
What about nsa?
监控到有关的反美的声音
There's elevated anti-american chatter
只是在一些平常的网站跟电话中
Coming from the usual web sites and telephone traffic,
但没有特指到这次袭击
But nothing specific to the attack.
谢谢你  蒂姆
Thank you, tim.
-15分钟后楼上见  -好的  阁下
- I'll see you upstairs in 15 minutes. -yes, ma'am.
这就意味着  我们最好的情报来源
Which means our best source of intelligence
还在我们的眼皮子底下
Is still right here under our noses.
你想到过我们得放这个混蛋一马吧
You realize we're gonna have to offer this bastard a free pass.
招降工作还得秘密进行
With coercive measures off the table,
这是我们唯一的选择了
It's our only option.
鲍尔锒铛入狱  而叛徒却逍遥法外
Bauer's going to prison, and a traitor walks.
这世界到底是怎么了
What's wrong with this picture?
我要和犯人单独呆会
I need a minute with the prisoner.
伯内特先生
Mr. burnett,
你将被联邦法律18章2381节
You will be charged with treason under title 18,
以叛国罪论处
Section 2381, of the united states code.
罪名是资敌
Giving aid and comfort to the enemy
和导致美国公民的死亡
And directly causing the death of american citizens.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
当然  你肯定要为自己辩解
Surely, you have something to say for yourself.
我要求见律师
I demand my right to counsel.
这没问题  伯内特先生
You'll have your counsel, mr. burnett,
但首先你得坦白一切
But first, you're going to tell me everything you know.
死都不会
Not in this lifetime.
-你刚说什么  -我说
-What did you say?  -i said,
死都不会
Not in this lifetime.
伯内特先生  别这么快就下定决心
Don't be so quick to make up your mind, mr. burnett.
为了阻止或减轻袭击的伤害
In exchange for information which stops
作为交换条件
Or significantly mitigates this attack,
总统可以特赦你的一切罪行
The president is prepared to grant you full immunity from prosecution.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
如果你和你的家人被挟持了
If you and your family are being threatened in any way...
你明白总统给你提供了什么样的条件吗
Do you realize what the president is offering you?
叛国罪是死罪  伯内特先生
Treason is a capital offense, mr. burnett.
如果你现在不合作
If you don't cooperate with us right now,
我会亲自过问此事
I will make it my personal mission
让你为你的罪行付出最终的代价
To see that you pay the ultimate price for your crimes.
我不赞同刑讯逼供  但就你的情况而言
I won't condone torture, but in your case,
我不会介意你被判处死刑
I would have no problem with the death penalty.
我律师在哪
Where's my lawyer?
-沃克  -是我
-Walker  -It's me.
医院那事如何了
That situation at the hospital you told me about?
我在调查中  拉里
Yeah, i'm on it, larry.
我追踪一个牌照  到了一家进出口公司
I traced a license plate to an import/export firm.
继续
Tell me.
刚那个护理员 刚与一群士兵汇合
The orderly i mentioned-- He just joined up with about a dozen soldiers.
非洲人  全副武装
Africans. heavily armed.
你在哪里
Where are you?
莱姆波恩码头44543号 约翰逊停车场附近
44543 lambourne marina, near johnson park.
我在地下仓库
I'm in the warehouse basement.
蕾妮  我们有情报显示
Renee, we have intel
朱玛将会发动另外一次袭击
On another attack by juma's people.
晚上7点后在首都
It's happening in d.c., sometime after 1900 hours.
这就是了  拉里  绝对没问题
This is it, larry. no question.
好  听着  别轻举妄动
All right, listen, sit tight.
-我带增援马上到  -快点
- I'm on my way with back up.  - Make it quick.
詹尼斯  准备一架直升机
Janis, scramble a chopper.
两分钟后到房顶
On the roof in two minutes.
-好的  但  -詹尼斯
-Okay. but also...  -Janis,
照做
Just do it.
我是拉里·莫斯
This is larry moss.
给我接首府警局
Put me through to metro police.
查特斯  特纳  跟我来
Charters, turner-- with me.
将军
General,
我父亲不见了
There is no sign of my father.
我刚和他通话
I just spoke with him.
但他不能来了
Unfortunately he won't be able to join us.
为什么
Why not?
为了给我们开辟安全通道离开这个国家
Because he got delayed in his attempt to secure safe passage for us
他被迫耽搁了
From the country.
那么长官
Then, sir,
请让我接替他在突击队的位置
Let me take his place on the assault team.
果真是虎父无犬子
Spoken like a true dubaku,
劳伦特
Laurent.
-但你也是我唯一的侦察兵  -但  将军
- But you are also my only reconnaissance officer. -but, general...
我需要你在外围提供情报
No, i need you on the perimeter to provide intelligence
并阻断任何救援部队
And also to disrupt whatever rescue operations there may be.
明白吗
Understood?
明白
Understood, sir.
做好最后准备
Make your final preparations.
-该出发了  -遵命
-It is time for us to go. -yes, sir.
拉里  快点  他们就要出发了
Larry, hurry, they're moving out.
我们还要10分钟
We're ten minutes away.
有没有可能是朱玛本人亲自率队
Is it possible that juma himself is leading this attack?
朱玛  为什么这么说
Juma? why do you say that?
我知道这不可思议  但我见到他了
I know it sounds crazy, but i swear that i just saw him.
什么  在这吗
What?! here?!
-你确定吗  -除非他有孪生兄弟
-Are you sure?  -unless he has an identical twin.
好  我会通知国土安全局的
All right, i'll alert homeland.
干得不错
Good work.
知道他们下个目标是什么吗
Any idea what the next target is?
不知道
Negative.
看看能否找出来  但听我说
See if you get a fix on that. but, listen,
别冒险
Don't take any chances.
好吗
All right?
知道
I won't.
长官
Sir.
-你应该看下医生  -我没事
-You should have an emt take a look at you.  -i'm fine.
-鲍尔被捕了吗  -是的
-Is bauer in custody?  -yes, sir.
-他被关起来了  -那没事了
-He's in holding.  -that'll be all.
托尼  我是比尔
Tony, it's bill.
比尔  杰克被捕了
Bill. jack's under arrest.
他们把他关起来了
They've got him locked down in a holding cell here.
-听我说  比尔  -你听我说
- Listen to me, bill...  - no, you listen.
我们还不知道袭击在哪发生
We still don't know where this attack's taking place.
伯内特没招供吗?
Burnett didn't break?
没  杰克被他们阻止了
No. they stopped jack before he could get the information.
伯内特不接受总统的特赦
And burnett didn't go for the president's immunity deal.
是你给杰克情报的  是吗
You were the one who brought jack the intel, right?
是的
That's right.
情报可靠吗
How real is it?
当然
Very.
谁是你的线人
Who was your contact?
一个和朱玛有直接联系的爱默生的手下
It was a guy in emerson's crew with a direct line to juma.
能搞定他吗
Any chance we get another crack at this guy?
不太可能
That's highly unlikely,
至少可以这么说
To say the least.
难道他死了吗
What are you telling me, he's dead?
对的
That's right?
我真希望你让我也加入
I wish to god you'd brought me in on this.
杰克不想牵连你
Jack didn't want to put you in that position.
事实上
For what it's worth,
他是想保护你  比尔
He was trying to protect you, bill.
至少  你总该有个备用计划吧
Did you have a fallback plan, at least?
伯内特同意赦免提议就是备用计划
Immunity for burnett was the fallback.
就这个啊  没别的路可走了吗
That's it? nothing else?
没
No.
没了
Nothing.
我试图联系蕾妮  但只能接通留言信箱
I keep trying renee, and i keep getting her voice mail.
出什么事了
What the hell's going on?
她手机有问题
There's something wrong with her phone.
手机出问题是什么意思
What do you mean, something's wrong?
5分钟前我刚和她通话
I just spoke to her five minutes ago.
能找出她的位置吗
Can you triangulate her position?
-找不出  -为什么
-I can't.  -why not?
没信号了
There's no signal.
要么是电池没电了
Either the battery's dead,
要么是手机坏掉了
Or her cell got damaged somehow.
好的  继续试
All right, keep trying.
-有消息就通知我  -好的
-Get back to me when you know something.  -okay.
从我们的位置
From our location
到入口大概100米
It is approximately 100 meters to the entrance.
从这开始
From this point forward,
保持无线电静默
We maintain radio silence
直到攻占了目标
Until the target is secure.
明白吗
Understood?
明白  长官
Yes, sir. understood.
你们都有自己的任务
You all have your assignments.
愿上帝与我们同在
May god be with us.
劳伦特  在船上待命
Laurent, take your position.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.